OK, so I'm here with Nico Anon, who plays the incredible Uncle Clifford on Pea Valley.
OK, this is a role that is impacting folks, not just in their viewership, but also in their community ship.
Right. And it speaks to what this episode of our podcast, Small Doses, is this week.
Side effects of black popular culture, how black pop culture can shift us.
And I would love for you all to drop in the comments any characters within black popular culture that may have shifted.
You and how they did so, because that's what makes our shit different.
That's true, because it lasts. So what's the impact that it had on you?
Ships. I had some shit that impacted me.
But you got to listen to the episode or watch the episode to find out.
So listen wherever you get your podcast and watch Small Doses side effects of black popular culture with Nico Anon on YouTube at Amanda Seals TV.
And what do you do when you say Stefan? Do you remember Stefan?
Of course I remember Stefan. Do y'all remember Stefan? See? Black culture.
I'm sorry.